<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MedKlick</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="select_hospital">Select Hospital</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="department">Department</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Register</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="minimum_password">Password too short, enter minimum 6 characters!</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed, check your email and password or sign up</string>
    <string name="change_email">Change Email</string>
    <string name="change_password">Change Password</string>
    <string name="send_password_reset_email">Send Password reset email</string>
    <string name="remove_user">Remove user</string>
    <string name="new_pass">New Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Firebase</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Fullname</string>
    <string name="btn_login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_register">Not a member? Get registered in Firebase now!</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Already registered. Login Me!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reset_password">ResetPasswordActivity</string>
    <string name="btn_forgot_password">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="btn_reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="btn_back"><![CDATA[<< Back]]></string>
    <string name="hint_new_email">New Email</string>
    <string name="btn_change">Change</string>
    <string name="btn_send">Send</string>
    <string name="btn_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="btn_sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="lbl_forgot_password">Forgot password?</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_msg">We just need your registered Email Id to sent you password reset instructions.</string>

    <string-array name="blood_group_array">
        <item>A+</item>
        <item>A-</item>
        <item>B+</item>
        <item>B-</item>
        <item>O+</item>
        <item>O-</item>
        <item>AB+</item>
        <item>AB-</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="blood_group_array2">
        <item>A</item>
        <item>B</item>
        <item>AB</item>
        <item>O</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="blood_units">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Check Reports</item>
        <item>Check Status</item>
        <item>About</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Hospital names Array -->
    <string-array name="hospital_array">
        <item>Hi-Tech Medical College and Hospital</item>
        <item>Ispat General Hospital</item>
        <item>Lifeline Hospital</item>
        <item>Shanti Memorial Hospital</item>
        <item>Vesaj Patel Hospital</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Departments Array-->
    <string-array name="departments_array">
        <item>Accident and emergency</item>
        <item>Anaesthetics</item>
        <item>Cardiology</item>
        <item>Critical care</item>
        <item>Ear, Nose and Throat</item>
        <item>Gastroenterology</item>
        <item>General surgery</item>
        <item>Gynaecology</item>
        <item>Haematology</item>
        <item>Nephrology</item>
        <item>Neurology</item>
        <item>Nutrition and dietetics</item>
        <item>Oncology</item>
        <item>Orthopaedics</item>
        <item>Physiotherapy</item>
        <item>Urology</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Wards Array -->
    <string-array name="ward_array">
        <item>General Ward</item>
        <item>Male Ward</item>
        <item>Female Ward</item>
        <item>Children Ward</item>
        <item>C.C.U.</item>
        <item>I.C.U.</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--Other Services Spinner Items-->
    <string-array name="vaccination">
        <item>Cholera</item>
        <item>Dengue</item>
        <item>Diptheria</item>
        <item>Hepatitis-A</item>
        <item>Hepatitis-B</item>
        <item>Hepatitis-E</item>
        <item>Hib</item>
        <item>HPV</item>
        <item>Influenza</item>
        <item>Malaria</item>
        <item>Measles</item>
        <item>Mumps</item>
        <item>Pertussis</item>
        <item>Rabis</item>
        <item>Tetanus</item>
        <item>Typhoid</item>
        <item>Tuberculosis</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tests">
        <item>PTT(Partial Thromboplastin Time)</item>
        <item>BMO(Basic Metabolic Panel)</item>
        <item>CBC (Complete Blood Count)</item>
        <item>Urine Test</item>
        <item>Allergy Test</item>
        <item>Blood Sugar Test</item>
        <item>Tumor Marker</item>
        <item>Immunity Test</item>
        <item>Hormone Test</item>
        <item>Genetic Test</item>
        <item>Haematology Test</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="diagonisis">
        <item>Ultra Sound</item>
        <item>CT Scan</item>
        <item>X-Ray</item>
        <item>IVP (Intravenous Pyleography</item>
        <item>Cholangiography</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="problem_areas">
        <item>Skin, Hair and Nails</item>
        <item>Men\'s Sexual Health</item>
        <item>Women\'s Sexual Health</item>
        <item>Bones and Joint Problem</item>
        <item>Physiotherapy</item>
        <item>Mental Health</item>
        <item>Digestive Problems</item>
        <item>Kidney and Urinary Problems</item>
        <item>Tooth and Mouth</item>
        <item>Ear, Nose, Throat</item>
        <item>Child Health</item>
        <item>Brain and Nerves</item>
        <item>Diet and Weight Problems</item>
        <item>General Health</item>
        <item>Eye and Vision</item>
        <item>Breathing Problems</item>
        <item>Diabetes and Hormonal Problems</item>
        <item>Heart</item>
        <item>Cancer</item>
        <item>I have some other problem...</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="terms_and_privacy_policy">
The Mavericks built the MedKlick app to provide hospital services. This SERVICE is provided by Mavericks at no cost
        and is intended for use as is.
\n\nThis page is used to inform the users regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure
        of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
\n\nIf you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation
        to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the
        Service. Mavericks will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
\n\nThe terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is
        accessible at MedKlick unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.
        \n\n<b>Information Collection and Use</b>
\n\nFor a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain
        personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Name, Email ID, Mobile Number
        and Address. The information that we request is retained on your device and is not collected by us in any way.
\n\nThe app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.
\n\nLink to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app:
\n\n
        <li><a href="https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/">Google Play Services</a></li>\n
        <li><a href="https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics">Firebase Analytics</a></li>
        \n\n<b>Log Data</b>
\n\nWe want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect
        data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data
        may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name,
        operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and
        date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.
        \n\n<b>Cookies</b>
\n\nCookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier.
        These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your device internal memory.
\n\nThis Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and
        libraries that use “cookies” to collection information and to improve their services. You have
        the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your
        device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.
        \n\n<b>Service Providers</b>
\n\nWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:

<li>To facilitate our Service;</li>\n
<li>To provide the Service on our behalf;</li>\n
<li>To perform Service-related services; or</li>\n
<li>To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</li>
\n\nWe want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information.
        The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to
        disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
        \n\n<b>Security</b>
\n\nWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially
        acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or
        method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
        \n\n<b>Links to Other Sites</b>
\n\nThis Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed
        to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you
        to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility
        for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
        \n\n<b>Children’s Privacy</b>
\n\nThese Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable
        information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with
        personal information, we immediately delete that from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and
        you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we
        will be able to take necessary actions.
        \n\n<b>Changes to This Privacy Policy</b>
\n\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for
        any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These
        changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.
        \n\n<b>Contact Us</b>
\n\nIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at mavericks@gmail.com.
\n\nThis privacy policy page was created at privacypolicytemplate.net and modified/generated by
        <a href="https://app-privacy-policy-generator.firebaseapp.com/">App Privacy Policy Generator</a>.
    </string>
    <string name="sudhansu_name">Sudhansu Barik</string>
    <string name="sudhansu_registration_number">1401216030</string>
    <string name="abhijeet_name">Abhijeet Chakraborty</string>
    <string name="abhijeet_registration_number">1401216081</string>
    <string name="reema_name">Reema Gupta</string>
    <string name="reema_registration_number">1401216024</string>
    <string name="doctor_a">Dr. Arpan</string>
    <string name="doctor_b">Dr. Basu</string>
    <string name="doctor_c">Dr. Chakraborty</string>
    <string name="doctor_d">Dr. Diwakar</string>
    <string name="fee_a">Rs. 250</string>
    <string name="fee_b">Rs. 250</string>
    <string name="fee_c">Rs. 250</string>
    <string name="fee_d">Rs. 250</string>

    <string name="about_medklick">
        <b>MedKlick</b> aims at improving the healthcare facility of Rourkela by making them easily available
        to the people of the city. It is a medical services application for people looking for healthcare services.
        Using MedKlick, one will be able to check the availability of doctor, take an appointment, find the
        best fit doctor on the basis of specialization, can check the availability of beds in hospitals,
        place a request for blood, find different ambulances available in the city, find the contact details
        of different hospitals around the city, can access the health reports, can ask for consultancy
        in case of emergency, and many more&#8230; This will be a boon to all the private as well as government
        hospitals. This will reduce the physical efforts and will also be time saving for patients.
    </string>

    <string-array name="payMode">
        <item>Debit Card</item>
        <item>Credit Card</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="doctor_appointment"><u>Doctor\'s Appointment</u></string>
    <string name="blood_request"><u>Blood Request Details</u></string>
    <string name="query"><u>Query</u></string>
</resources>
